<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RainbowMarks Photography</title>
    <description>RainbowMarks Photography, Wildwood, Missouri</description>
    <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://rainbowmarks.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:57:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>NASA PACE Falcon 9 Rocket Launch</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In February of 2024, I had the pleasure of spending some time in Florida for a work conference. While there, I kept an eye on the forecast and space launch schedule to see if I might catch a rocket launch while in town. SpaceX was planning to launch a Falcon 9 with the NASA PACE payload. The launch ended up being delayed for 3 days, finally happening early in the morning on February 8th, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was not a publicly accessible launch, and I’m not sure why, but my assumption is that Falcon 9 launches are getting so frequent nowadays that late night/early morning launches are too much work from an organization perspective to try to allow the public access to the Cape to see launches. So, what does this mean? The public can still watch; they just have to do it from remote locations, not on the Cape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-800-d92b355ad.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mission Control Morrell Operations Center Entry&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-200-d92b355ad.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-400-d92b355ad.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-800-d92b355ad.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-1600-d92b355ad.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-2000-d92b355ad.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-800-d20ce17ef.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mission Control Morrell Operations Center Display&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-200-d20ce17ef.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-400-d20ce17ef.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-800-d20ce17ef.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-1600-d20ce17ef.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-2000-d20ce17ef.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where did I watch the launch? I was fortunate enough to be invited to join a couple of remote family members who live and even work on the Cape, so I got special access. The morning started out with a quick tour of Mission Control, yes, Mission Control for the launch! There are actually two different rooms for MC, one for the active launch, and one for anything else going on or tours, so we got to walk through the empty mission control room and look into the active room. With Falcon 9 launches, the number of people in mission control is pretty minimal, which was surprising to see considering what was occurring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-800-77caf8f5b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mission Control at Morrell Operations Center with Me!&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-200-77caf8f5b.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-400-77caf8f5b.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-800-77caf8f5b.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-1600-77caf8f5b.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-2000-77caf8f5b.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-800-22a541a5e.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mission Control at Morrell Operations Center&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-200-22a541a5e.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-400-22a541a5e.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-800-22a541a5e.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-1600-22a541a5e.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-2000-22a541a5e.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was the best part about the Mission Control tour? The laugh I got in the bathroom! Check out this sign. If the people who are launching rockets into space can’t even hit the toilet, how are they going to land on Mars? (sorry, I couldn’t resist)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-800-93b5aef0b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mission Control Urinals&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-200-93b5aef0b.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-400-93b5aef0b.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-800-93b5aef0b.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-1600-93b5aef0b.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-2000-93b5aef0b.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then came the launch itself. I won’t share exact details on where we were for the launch, but boy was that an experience! This Falcon 9 rocket was launching towards the south, something that a NASA payload hadn’t done in 50+ years, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thor-Ablestar&quot;&gt;the last time on November 30th, 1960, having a problem during launch and rumored to kill a cow in Cuba&lt;/a&gt;. After the launch, and I mean, almost right after, like 7 minutes, the rocket would come back and land also on the Cape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were set up to watch the launch, knowing that we didn’t have the best spot to view the landing pad, but had thoughts of maybe trying to drive over to catch the landing. Long story short, we didn’t make it over to see the landing, we took too long watching the launch and nearly missed the landing altogether as we were driving west towards it when the sky lit up with what looked like lightning then the sun as the rocket reignited for landing along with sonic booms as it broke the sound barrier. I managed to stick the camera out the window of the SUV and got a shot or two, but nothing great of the landing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a great experience, it had been 14 years since I saw my first shuttle launch, also a night launch with access to the Cape from an employee. This launch had a little less excitement as the Shuttle launch we had to rush to get on the bus to depart our viewing location because of the risk of an acid cloud blowing back at us!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t wait for my next launch, and definitely am taking my family with me next time so they can experience it too!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/03/NASAPACELaunch</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/03/NASAPACELaunch</guid>
        
        <category>space</category>
        
        <category>rocket</category>
        
        <category>launch</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Capture the Essence of Victory with RainbowMarks Photography at the Blue Note Cup 2024! Blue Note Cup 2024 - Game Photos</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;-book-your-game-today&quot;&gt;📸 Book Your Game Today!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At RainbowMarks Photography, we’re thrilled to announce our exclusive photography services for the Blue Note Cup 2024! Get ready to immortalize your team’s moments of glory on the ice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;exclusive-offer-225game&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exclusive Offer: $225/Game&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For just $225, secure a spot on our shooting schedule and ensure your game is captured through our lenses with precision and creativity. But that’s not all - your booking grants you:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professionally Processed Photos:&lt;/strong&gt; After the game, access and download the high-quality, professionally processed images of your game directly from our website.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10% Off Physical Prints:&lt;/strong&gt; Dive into your game’s photo gallery online and order physical prints to keep those memories tangible. Enjoy a 10% discount on every print, turning moments into lasting mementos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-choose-rainbowmarks-photography&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Choose RainbowMarks Photography?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on Your Team:&lt;/strong&gt; By booking ahead, you guarantee that we capture the essence of your team’s performance, focusing on the moments that matter most to you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High-Quality Imagery:&lt;/strong&gt; With RainbowMarks Photography, expect nothing less than professional-grade photos that capture the intensity, emotion, and triumph of your games.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easy Access &amp;amp; Ordering:&lt;/strong&gt; After the game, effortlessly download your photos and order prints from the convenience of your home.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;booking-is-essential&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Booking Is Essential!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, to ensure we cover your game and concentrate on your team, &lt;strong&gt;advance booking is necessary&lt;/strong&gt;. Spots fill up fast, especially for an event as anticipated as the Blue Note Cup 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;capture-the-moment-relive-the-glory&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capture the Moment, Relive the Glory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t let these fleeting moments slip away. Book RainbowMarks Photography now and keep the spirit of the game alive through stunning photographs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📅 &lt;strong&gt;Schedule Your Game:&lt;/strong&gt; Contact us today (650)260-8344 to secure your booking and take the first step towards capturing the heart and soul of your team’s journey at the Blue Note Cup 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/02/BlueNoteCupPhotography</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/02/BlueNoteCupPhotography</guid>
        
        <category>hockey</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bald Eagles in Clarksville, Missouri January 2024</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On Sunday morning, the 21st of January, I headed up to Clarksville Missouri to look for Bald Eagles along the Mississippi River.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I arrived just after sunrise (next time I’ll leave earlier) and immediately saw two Bald Eagles flying just north of the lock and dam. I knew it was going to be a good day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I parked in the public parking near the lock and dam and immediately started getting my equipment ready to get setup. I took a monopod, instead of a tripod for the day, though I am not sure if that was the best choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other photographers who were there had tripods, while I had a little more mobility than they did, I feel like I could have used the stability of a tripod. I’ll have to try that next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a rather cold morning, and while I thought I was prepared for the chill, I wasn’t. Next time I’ll go I’ll be sure to take a mask and better gloves with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Eagles south of the damn were pretty active just after sunrise, with bursts of activity as they were trying to find fish in the river.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After an hour or so in Clarksville, I headed south on 79. I ended up driving through Clarence Cannon National Wildlife Refuge. I also stopped for a bit in Winfield, Missouri and found a few more Bald Eagles hunting there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here in the gallery you can see a couple of the shots I was able to capture, I look forward to going back again soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve posted a 36 megabyte image that has 99 shots of one particular Bald Eagle going through the motions of catching and flying off with a fish. You can see the full high resolution photo here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rainbowmarks.com/img/Birds2024-2.jpg&quot;&gt;Bald Eagle Catching Fish&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/BaldEaglesClarksville</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/BaldEaglesClarksville</guid>
        
        <category>wildlife</category>
        
        <category>nature</category>
        
        <category>bald eagles</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>January 20th weekend Hockey!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Chesterfield Falcons had two games the weekend of January 20th, 2024. The AI generated game summaries are below!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-summary-chesterfield-falcons-10ua1-vs-kirkwood-stars-10ua1&quot;&gt;Game Summary: Chesterfield Falcons 10UA1 vs Kirkwood Stars 10UA1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;location-maryville-university-hockey-center-shanahan-rink&quot;&gt;Location: Maryville University Hockey Center, Shanahan Rink&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;date-saturday-january-20th-2024&quot;&gt;Date: Saturday January 20th, 2024&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an exhilarating display of youth ice hockey, the Chesterfield Falcons 10UA1 faced off against the Kirkwood Stars 10UA1 at the Maryville University Hockey Center on the Shanahan rink. The matchup was highly anticipated, especially considering the history of the two teams. In their previous encounters, the Kirkwood Stars had dominated, winning 10-2 and 7-0. However, this game proved to be a stark contrast to their past meetings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the drop of the puck, it was evident that the Falcons had come with a new level of determination and skill. Both teams exhibited remarkable talent and teamwork, making it a thrilling game to watch. The Falcons, showing significant improvement from their previous games, matched the Stars play for play, leading to a nail-bitingly close contest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the game, the lead oscillated between the two teams, with each side scoring impressive goals. The young athletes on the ice demonstrated not only skill but also sportsmanship and a passion for the game, which was infectious for the audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the final buzzer sounded, the scoreboard read 6-6, marking the end of regulation time in a draw. This result was a testament to the hard work and improvement of the Chesterfield Falcons, who managed to hold their own against a team that had previously bested them with significant margins. For the Kirkwood Stars, it was a reminder of the unpredictability and competitive spirit inherent in sports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, this game was not just a display of young talent, but also a story of resilience, improvement, and the unyielding spirit of competition. Both the Chesterfield Falcons and the Kirkwood Stars should be proud of their performance in a game that will surely be remembered for its intensity and the remarkable skill displayed by all players involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-summary-chesterfield-falcons-10ua1-vs-affton-all-americans-10ua1&quot;&gt;Game Summary: Chesterfield Falcons 10UA1 vs Affton All-Americans 10UA1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;location-maryville-university-hockey-center-shanahan-rink-1&quot;&gt;Location: Maryville University Hockey Center, Shanahan Rink&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;date-sunday-january-21st-2024&quot;&gt;Date: Sunday January 21st, 2024&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Chesterfield Falcons 10UA1 continued their impressive run in youth ice hockey with a solid victory over the Affton All-Americans 10UA1, finishing with a score of 4-1. This game, held at the same rink where they had tied the day before with another team, showcased the Falcons’ resilience and skill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Affton All-Americans started the game on a high note, with Chase Cotton opening the scoring with 6:55 left in the first period. This early lead set the stage for an intense game, but the Falcons quickly responded. Demonstrating their competitive spirit and ability to handle pressure, Chesterfield’s defenseman Matthew Pitcher tied the game just 1:10 later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Falcons’ momentum continued to build as Bennett Suda attempted to dump the puck in front of the goal, leading to an unexpected but welcome goal, putting Chesterfield in the lead. The first period ended with the Falcons leading 2-1, a testament to their quick recovery and offensive prowess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the second period, the Falcons maintained their dominance. Levi James extended their lead with a goal with 5:59 remaining, showcasing the depth of talent in the Chesterfield team. The Falcons’ defense and goaltender also deserve commendation for their performance in keeping the All-Americans at bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third period saw Chesterfield solidifying their lead. Bennett Suda, assisted by Lucky Huntebrinker, scored with 6:54 remaining, bringing the score to 4-1. This goal underscored the Falcons’ strategic play and effective teamwork throughout the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The final whistle confirmed Chesterfield’s victory, with a repeat scoreline of 4-1 against the Affton All-Americans, similar to their previous encounter. This win further established the Falcons as a formidable team in the league, capable of maintaining consistency and showcasing improvement game after game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the Affton All-Americans, despite the loss, the team’s early goal and overall performance highlighted their potential and the competitive nature of the league. Both teams exhibited commendable skill and sportsmanship, making it an enjoyable game for spectators and a valuable experience for the young athletes involved.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/January20thHockey</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/January20thHockey</guid>
        
        <category>events</category>
        
        <category>hockey</category>
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Book Your 2024 Events with RainbowMarks Photography – Capture Every Moment!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you planning an event in 2024 around Wildwood, Missouri, or in the broader St. Louis area? Looking for a professional photography service that captures the essence of your special moments? Look no further than &lt;strong&gt;RainbowMarks Photography&lt;/strong&gt;, a leader in &lt;strong&gt;event photography in Wildwood, MO&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;capturing-the-spirit-of-the-midwest&quot;&gt;Capturing the Spirit of the Midwest&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While based in Wildwood, our lenses capture events far and wide across the Midwest. RainbowMarks Photography is not only a top choice in &lt;strong&gt;professional photography in St. Louis&lt;/strong&gt;, but also across the region. We’ve covered a diverse range of events, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The 2023 MR340 Paddle Race on the Missouri River, showcasing our skill in &lt;a href=&quot;https://rainbowmarks.com/MR340/2023/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Missouri River paddle race photos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The action-packed Miner Tough weekend with running and mountain biking events, highlighting our expertise in &lt;strong&gt;sports event photography&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Unbound Gravel race in Emporia, Kansas, where we delivered stunning &lt;strong&gt;Unbound Gravel Emporia, KS photography&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our cameras are adept at capturing the spirit of these dynamic events, and we’re eager to bring the same energy and professionalism to your occasion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;specialized-sports-event-photography&quot;&gt;Specialized Sports Event Photography&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At RainbowMarks Photography, we understand the dynamics of various sports. That’s why we offer specialized photography services for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Baseball&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Football&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hockey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lacrosse&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Field Hockey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Soccer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Auto Racing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And many more sports! Whether it’s a fast-paced hockey game or strategic soccer plays, our photographers excel in capturing every pivotal moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;flexible-photography-packages&quot;&gt;Flexible Photography Packages&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding the diverse needs of different events, we offer various packages:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Daily rates for comprehensive coverage.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weekend packages for extended events.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rates for individual games or matches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;beyond-digital-images&quot;&gt;Beyond Digital Images&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Choose from a range of photo products:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;High-quality digital images for download or purchase.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hard copy prints.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Large canvas and vinyl prints for impactful displays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;book-early-for-2024&quot;&gt;Book Early for 2024!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 calendar fills up, we encourage early bookings, especially for weekends. [Contact us for &lt;strong&gt;Midwest event photography packages&lt;/strong&gt; and pricing details]](https://www.chrishammond.com/Contact).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RainbowMarks Photography&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Event Photography in Wildwood, MO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Serving St. Louis and the Midwest&lt;br /&gt;
“Capturing Every Moment with Color and Passion”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/Contact&quot;&gt;Book Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/&quot;&gt;Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/rainbowmarksphoto&quot;&gt;Like us on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📞 Contact us today to discuss your event needs and let us help you preserve your memories in vivid detail. Remember, the best moments are fleeting, but our photographs make them last forever!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/BookYour2024Events</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/BookYour2024Events</guid>
        
        <category>events</category>
        
        <category>bookings</category>
        
        <category>book</category>
        
        <category>digital</category>
        
        <category>downloads</category>
        
        <category>packages</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Pricing! 30% reduction in price on most physical items!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming into 2024, we’re making some changes! We’ve reduced our pricing for physical items (prints, frames, metal, acrylic, canvas, mugs, etc.) by up to 30%! We plan to keep these prices for the foreseeable future!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;get-ordering&quot;&gt;Get Ordering!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find all our photos from the last couple of years available for purchase in our &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/&quot;&gt;Galleries&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-digital-pricing-and-offering&quot;&gt;New Digital Pricing and Offering&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re offering a lower-resolution digital download that you can use on social media for $10. At this time, we will no longer be offering high-resolution digital downloads of our work except for special occasions and prepaid events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope you enjoy our work, and we look forward to seeing you at an event soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;planning-an-event-in-2024&quot;&gt;Planning an event in 2024?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re booking now for 2024! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/Contact&quot;&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt; today! Reach out early and get discounted event pricing!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/12/HolidayPrices</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/12/HolidayPrices</guid>
        
        <category>sale</category>
        
        <category>holiday</category>
        
        <category>christmas</category>
        
        <category>prints</category>
        
        <category>physical</category>
        
        <category>digital</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shop the Year&apos;s Best Moments with RainbowMarks Photography&apos;s Black Friday &amp; Cyber Monday Sales!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As 2023 draws to a close, RainbowMarks Photography invites you to revisit the year’s most unforgettable events through our exclusive collection of photographs. This Black Friday and Cyber Monday, decorate your space or gift a piece of history with our special discounts on physical prints and digital downloads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;your-year-of-memories-awaits&quot;&gt;Your Year of Memories Awaits!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the electric energy of summer festivals to the serene landscapes of autumn, our photographers have been there to capture it all. Now, you can own a piece of this year’s history with a special Black Friday and Cyber Monday discount on our entire catalog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;25% Off Physical Prints&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Relive your favorite events with the tangible beauty of physical prints. Apply the code &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;2023BG25&lt;/code&gt; at checkout to secure your discount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;30% Off Digital Downloads&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Prefer to keep things digital? We’ve got you covered with 30% off all digital downloads. Just use the code &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;2023BG30&lt;/code&gt; when completing your purchase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-shop-rainbowmarks-photography&quot;&gt;Why Shop RainbowMarks Photography?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Curation&lt;/strong&gt;: Our collection features the best shots from each event, selected by our professional photographers.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High-Quality Imagery&lt;/strong&gt;: Every photo is meticulously processed to ensure you receive gallery-quality imagery.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exclusive Content&lt;/strong&gt;: These photos are more than just images; they’re unique moments that you won’t find anywhere else.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;seal-the-deal-before-time-runs-out&quot;&gt;Seal the Deal Before Time Runs Out!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These special offers are valid until Cyber Monday, 11/27/2023, so act fast! Visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/&quot;&gt;RainbowMarks Photography&lt;/a&gt; now to explore the year’s highlights and claim your favorites. Don’t forget to use the codes &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;2023BG25&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;2023BG30&lt;/code&gt; at checkout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dive into the past year’s memories and make them a permanent part of your life with RainbowMarks Photography.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/11/Blackfriday</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/11/Blackfriday</guid>
        
        <category>sale</category>
        
        <category>holiday</category>
        
        <category>thanksgiving</category>
        
        <category>blackfriday</category>
        
        <category>cybermonday</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MO Judges Cup Gymnastics - November 10, 2023</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Photos from Olympia Ellisville Xcel Silver competing at the MO Judges Cup 2023 Gymnastics Competition at the Olympia Manchester facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Gymnastics/MO-Judges-Cup-2023&quot;&gt;Click here to View the Full Gallery and / Purchase Photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/frame/slideshow?key=MXwxM2&amp;amp;speed=3&amp;amp;transition=fade&amp;amp;autoStart=1&amp;amp;captions=0&amp;amp;navigation=0&amp;amp;playButton=0&amp;amp;randomize=0&amp;amp;transitionSpeed=2&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/11/MoJudgesCup</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/11/MoJudgesCup</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>gymnastics</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chesterfield Falcons 10U-A1 Shine at the Leprechaun Lashout Tournament</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Chesterfield Falcons 10U-A1 team showcased their talent and determination at the prestigious Leprechaun Lashout tournament held at the iconic Notre Dame University. Here’s a recap of their journey game by game:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-1-chesterfield-falcons-vs-chicago-flames&quot;&gt;Game 1: Chesterfield Falcons vs. Chicago Flames&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the tournament’s opening game held at the Ice Box, the Falcons asserted their dominance early on. &lt;strong&gt;Daniel Hammond&lt;/strong&gt; spearheaded the charge with the opening goal, setting the tone for the rest of the game. Although the official scoreboard showcased an impressive 8-0 win, sources say the Falcons had notched up at least 12 goals! &lt;strong&gt;Braxton Vatterott&lt;/strong&gt; was particularly scintillating, with a hattrick under his belt. Adding another feather to their cap, &lt;strong&gt;Miles McCarthy&lt;/strong&gt; recorded his first shutout of the season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-2-chesterfield-falcons-vs-joliet-jaguars&quot;&gt;Game 2: Chesterfield Falcons vs. Joliet Jaguars&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning’s clash with the Joliet Jaguars Squirt 1 team on the “Lefty Smith” rink proved to be a challenging one for the Falcons. The Jaguars’ strategy of utilizing breakaways put them in the driver’s seat, ultimately clinching a 7-3 victory. Despite the loss, the Falcons learned valuable lessons in teamwork and resilience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-3-chesterfield-falcons-vs-fox-motors-hockey-club&quot;&gt;Game 3: Chesterfield Falcons vs. Fox Motors Hockey Club&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bouncing back from the morning’s setback, the Falcons were in splendid form against the Fox Motors Hockey Club on Notre Dame’s Olympic rink. Securing a comfortable 5-2 victory, the win was a testament to the team’s fighting spirit. Although they conceded two late goals, the Falcons’ performance ensured their place in the championship showdown. The victory was made even sweeter with a memorable team photo session at the Compton Family Ice Arena.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;championship-game-chesterfield-falcons-vs-joliet-jaguars&quot;&gt;Championship Game: Chesterfield Falcons vs. Joliet Jaguars&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday morning brought with it the promise of redemption as the Falcons once again faced the Jaguars. Although the Jaguars took the early lead, it was &lt;strong&gt;Daniel “Hammer” Hammond&lt;/strong&gt; who dazzled with his finesse, tying the game with a remarkable goal. The momentum swung in the Falcons’ favor when &lt;strong&gt;Bennett Suda&lt;/strong&gt; found the net, giving them a lead they wouldn’t relinquish. &lt;strong&gt;Jasper Boyher&lt;/strong&gt; put the cherry on top with a late empty-netter, ensuring the Falcons clinched the Squirt AA title of the Leprechaun Lashout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;in-conclusion&quot;&gt;In Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Leprechaun Lashout tournament was a testament to the Chesterfield Falcons 10U-A1 team’s skill, determination, and heart. They fought, they learned, and they emerged victorious. Kudos to every player, coach, and supporter for this remarkable achievement!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Hockey/23-24-Falcons-10U-A1/Leprechaun-Lashout&quot;&gt;View the full gallery with 600+ photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/11/leprechaunlashout/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/11/leprechaunlashout/</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>hockey</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Affton Americans Youth Ice Hockey Photos - 10U-A1 10-8-2023</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Summary: Affton Americans vs. Chesterfield Falcons (10U A1 Squirt Hockey Match on 10/8/2023)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Hockey/23-24-Falcons-10U-A1/10-8-2023-vs-Affton-Americans&quot;&gt;View the full gallery with 160+ photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an exciting clash between the Affton Americans and the Chesterfield Falcons, the Falcons soared to victory, securing their first win of the season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Details&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teams&lt;/strong&gt;: Affton Americans (Home) vs. Chesterfield Falcons (Visiting)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Score&lt;/strong&gt;: Affton Americans 2 - 5 Chesterfield Falcons&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scoring by Periods&lt;/strong&gt;:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;1st Period: Affton Americans 0 - Chesterfield Falcons 2&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;2nd Period: Affton Americans 2 - Chesterfield Falcons 2&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;3rd Period: Affton Americans 0 - Chesterfield Falcons 1&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shots on Goal&lt;/strong&gt;:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Affton Americans: 1st Period (6), 2nd Period (4), 3rd Period (7), Total (17)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Chesterfield Falcons: 1st Period (6), 2nd Period (11), 3rd Period (4), Total (21)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Goal Scorers&lt;/strong&gt;:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Chesterfield Falcons: Huntebrinker, Sciarratta, Ryan Pitcher, and Jackson Franklin.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Affton Americans: Scoring details not specified.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both teams displayed a commendable performance on the rink. Chesterfield’s Huntebrinker, Sciarratta, Ryan Pitcher, and Jackson Franklin played a pivotal role in their team’s success, each finding the back of the net. The Falcons were consistent in their goal-scoring across all periods, while the Americans made a strong comeback in the second period, only to be held scoreless in the third.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to the Chesterfield Falcons for achieving their first victory of the season. Both teams showcased great skill and sportsmanship, making it an engaging watch for all spectators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Hockey/23-24-Falcons-10U-A1/10-8-2023-vs-Affton-Americans&quot;&gt;View the full gallery with 160+ photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested in having your team’s ice hockey game photographed? &lt;a href=&quot;/events/hockey/&quot;&gt;Read more about our Ice Hockey Photo packages&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/10/AfftonAmericansIceHockeyPhotos/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/10/AfftonAmericansIceHockeyPhotos/</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>hockey</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
