<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RainbowMarks Photography</title>
    <description>RainbowMarks Photography, specializing in event photography in and around St. Louis Missouri.</description>
    <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://rainbowmarks.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 17:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 17:53:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mountain Bike Team Photos</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This weekend I had the pleasure of shooting team photos for a local Mountain Bike team, part of the Missouri Interscholastic Cycling League NICA (National Interscholastic Cycling Association).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the gallery here on this page are a couple of the results along with a link to the larger gallery. If you’re MTB Team is ready for a photo shoot &lt;a href=&quot;https://forms.gle/nW53hFmwBrNjqdg96&quot;&gt;be sure to reach out ASAP&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 14:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Blog/2024/10/mountain-bike-team-photos</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Blog/2024/10/mountain-bike-team-photos</guid>
        
        
        <category>team</category>
        
        <category>mtb</category>
        
        <category>bike</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Northern Lights over Missouri and the Mississipi River</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Blog/2024/10/how-to-photograph-the-northern-lights&quot;&gt;Yesterday I posted about how to take photos of the Northern Lights&lt;/a&gt;, here are the results of my own process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night was a busy night. My wife has a dressage show this weekend, so I was doing the bachelor dad thing for the start of the evening. Running one kid to gymnastics and then taking the other to hockey practice. Before these two events I packed up all the camera gear I thought I was going to need for the evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After hockey I grabbed a quick bite to eat and then transferred kid #2 to Natalie on her way home, and then I headed north. My goal was to try to get somewhere to see the northern lights with some water in the foreground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking at dark sky maps I considered heading to Mark Twain Lake, but I was concerned that I wouldn’t be able to find a decent spot and that I would be too late by the time I got there. Instead, I headed up 79 towards Clarksville MO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way I looked up boat ramps and picked one in Clarksville. Upon arrival I decided there was too much extra light, so I continued one ramp north of Clarksville to a great little place (Silo Access Boat Ramp). When I pulled in, I realized it had some camping spots with a few folks in trailers and a car or two parked nearby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was dark, and I was able to park pretty close to the Mississippi River. I quickly got out of the car and setup to take photos for a couple of hours. This aurora event was unlike any previous one I’ve experienced (2 in the past 18 months). It was amazing. As my eyes adjusted to the dark sky the lights and colors really started to pop. To the point that I was getting distracted trying to get the cameras setup to just look and take it all in visually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The photos here are some of the selected photos taken on my Canon R5 with a 15-35mm lens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a timelapse of those and more photos all together:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;550&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/HaXKIvGcx60?si=HgiuOvghybsE1yHr&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 11:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Blog/2024/10/northern-lights-over-missouri</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Blog/2024/10/northern-lights-over-missouri</guid>
        
        
        <category>night sky</category>
        
        <category>space</category>
        
        <category>astro</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Photograph the Northern Lights: A Guide to Capturing Nature’s Spectacular Light Show</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With the recent influx of solar activity the ability for more parts of the United States to see the Northern Lights (aurora borealis) has increased many times over the past year. We are in a peak phase of sun activity this year and may continue to have opportunities for the near future, but you never know, so if you’ve got an opportunity to get outside, do it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Blog/2024/10/northern-lights-over-missouri&quot;&gt;See some of the output from these tips&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Northern Lights, or Aurora Borealis, are one of the most breathtaking natural phenomena to witness. Capturing them through photography, however, can be tricky due to the unique conditions and low-light environment. Here’s a comprehensive guide on how to best photograph the Northern Lights and come home with stunning images.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-choose-the-right-time-and-location&quot;&gt;1. Choose the Right Time and Location&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Northern Lights are most visible in areas close to the magnetic poles, such as Norway, Iceland, Alaska, and parts of Canada. Timing is key — the best chances for viewing occur during the winter months when the nights are longer and skies are clearer. It’s also important to check solar activity forecasts, as auroras are more intense during high solar activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pro Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; Apps like My Aurora Forecast or websites like spaceweather.gov can help predict when the aurora will be active in your location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;october-2024-thoughts&quot;&gt;October 2024 thoughts:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event currently scheduled for October 10th and 11th 2024 may be visible from as far south in the US as Alabama. Everyone in the country should be thinking about getting outside these evenings to see if they can find the Northern Lights. There is no guarantee that you’ll see them, but you definitely won’t if you stay inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-essential-gear-for-northern-lights-photography&quot;&gt;2. Essential Gear for Northern Lights Photography&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don’t need a fancy setup to capture the Northern Lights, but the right equipment will ensure your photos are sharp and detailed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Camera:&lt;/strong&gt; A DSLR or mirrorless camera with manual settings is ideal.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lens:&lt;/strong&gt; Use a wide-angle lens (14-24mm) with a fast aperture (f/2.8 or lower) to capture as much of the sky as possible.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tripod:&lt;/strong&gt; A sturdy tripod is a must. You’ll be shooting long exposures, so keeping the camera still is crucial.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote Shutter or Timer:&lt;/strong&gt; To avoid camera shake, use a remote shutter or set a delay timer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pro Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; Bring extra batteries — cold weather can drain them quickly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-set-up-your-camera&quot;&gt;3. Set Up Your Camera&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding your camera’s settings is essential to photographing the Northern Lights. Since each aurora display varies in brightness and movement, experimenting with these settings will help you capture the perfect shot:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aperture:&lt;/strong&gt; Set your lens to its widest aperture (f/2.8 or lower) to allow maximum light.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ISO:&lt;/strong&gt; Start with an ISO of 800-1600. If the lights are faint, increase the ISO, but be careful not to introduce too much noise.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shutter Speed:&lt;/strong&gt; Adjust based on the intensity of the lights. A starting point is 5-15 seconds. If the aurora is moving fast, use shorter exposures (5-10 seconds) to avoid blurring the details.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Manually set your focus to infinity or focus on a distant light source, such as stars or a faraway mountain. Use live view mode to fine-tune the sharpness.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pro Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; Take a few test shots and zoom in to ensure the stars are sharp. Autofocus often struggles in low light, so manual focus is usually best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-framing-and-composition&quot;&gt;4. Framing and Composition&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the Northern Lights are the stars of the show, incorporating foreground elements like trees, mountains, or water can make your images more dynamic. The key is balance — don’t let the foreground overpower the aurora, but use it to add depth and context to your shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Silhouettes:&lt;/strong&gt; A tree line or cabin can add drama without distracting from the lights.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reflections:&lt;/strong&gt; If you’re near a body of water, try to capture the reflection of the lights in the water for an added layer of beauty.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rule of Thirds:&lt;/strong&gt; Use this composition rule to position the horizon on the lower third of the frame, giving the sky more space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pro Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; Use a headlamp with a red filter when setting up. Red light won’t impact your night vision as much as white light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-post-processing-tips&quot;&gt;5. Post-Processing Tips&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve captured your photos, post-processing can help bring out the beauty of the aurora.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise Reduction:&lt;/strong&gt; Shooting at high ISOs can introduce noise, so use software like Adobe Lightroom or Photoshop to reduce noise in your images.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contrast and Exposure:&lt;/strong&gt; Enhance the vibrancy and detail of the Northern Lights by adjusting the contrast, highlights, and shadows. Be careful not to over-edit and lose the natural look.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sharpening:&lt;/strong&gt; A bit of sharpening can bring out the stars and details in the aurora.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-patience-and-perseverance&quot;&gt;6. Patience and Perseverance&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Northern Lights are unpredictable. Sometimes they may appear for only a few minutes, while other times they could dance for hours. Be patient, keep shooting, and embrace the serenity of the experience. Often, the best shots come from waiting through long, cold nights for the perfect moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pro Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; Always dress warmly and bring hot drinks or snacks to keep comfortable during long shooting sessions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photographing the Northern Lights can be challenging but also immensely rewarding. With the right equipment, settings, and a bit of patience, you’ll be able to capture stunning images of one of nature’s most magical displays. Remember to enjoy the moment, as seeing the aurora with your own eyes is an unforgettable experience — the photos are just the icing on the cake!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Blog/2024/10/how-to-photograph-the-northern-lights</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Blog/2024/10/how-to-photograph-the-northern-lights</guid>
        
        
        <category>night sky</category>
        
        <category>space</category>
        
        <category>astro</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Solo Nationals Photo Galleries</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🚗🏁 Exciting News! 🏁🚗&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve just finished uploading over 23,000 photos from the 2024 Solo National Championships, ProSolo Finale, and CAM Invitational—all held in Lincoln, Nebraska from August 30th to September 6th, 2024! &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Autocross/2024-Solo-National-Championships&quot;&gt;You can check them out here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔍 Find your car: All of the photos are tagged with car and class numbers. For example, searching “42FS” in the gallery will bring up all tagged photos of that car, this should make it really easy to find your own car!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📸 Get your photos: High-resolution digital downloads are available for $25 each. Want ALL photos of your car? You can get them for $200, or $275 if you participated in ProSolo too! This includes a custom private gallery delivered within 24-48 hours. &lt;a href=&quot;https://rainbowmarks.square.site/product/2024-solo-nationals/4&quot;&gt;Visit this link&lt;/a&gt; to purchase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve already purchased the event special package you should have received an email with information on how to access! If not, please reach out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the memories and share your favorites! 🎉📷 #SoloNats #ProSolo #CAMInvitational #Autocross
&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Autocross/2024-Solo-National-Championships&quot;&gt;Click on the Gallery link here on this page for all the photos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/09/SoloNationalsGallery/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/09/SoloNationalsGallery/</guid>
        
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>race</category>
        
        <category>car</category>
        
        <category>solo</category>
        
        <category>autocross</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2024 Bommarito 500 IndyCar Photos</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I had the pleasure of once again getting to wander around World Wide Technology Raceway for the IndyCar event this weekend, the Bommarito 500! The race was held on August 17th, 2024 in Madison, Illinois.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2021/08/August-21-2021-IndyCar-Race-At-WWT-Raceway&quot;&gt;My first IndyCar experience was back in 2021&lt;/a&gt; and this time hoped to improve on the shots I took during that race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was fortunate enough to have access to the VIP suites building and planted myself on the top of the roof for the start of the race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From there I wandered down into the infield and spent the majority of the race along the fence in turn 3. Many of the turn 3 shots are fairly repetitive but I was over there trying to see what I could make the camera do and how the setting sun would effect things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Towards the end of the race I made my way back over near the front straight to see if I could get anywhere close to the finish for some shots but ended up not getting anything there worth posting, perhaps next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here in the gallery we have a handful of shots, &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Bommarito-500&quot;&gt;check out the main gallery for 200 photos from the race&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/08/Bommarito500Photos/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/08/Bommarito500Photos/</guid>
        
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>race</category>
        
        <category>racing</category>
        
        <category>cars</category>
        
        <category>indycar</category>
        
        <category>wwt</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2024 Tire Rack SCCA Solo Nationals Photos</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;update-check-out-our-2024-solo-nationals-photo-announcement-post&quot;&gt;Update: &lt;a href=&quot;https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/09/SoloNationalsGallery/&quot;&gt;Check out our 2024 Solo Nationals Photo Announcement Post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get ready, motorsport enthusiasts! RainbowMarks Photography is thrilled to announce our coverage of the 2024 Tire Rack SCCA Solo Nationals in Lincoln, Nebraska. This iconic event is the pinnacle of Solo competition, and we’re geared up to capture the high-octane action from start to finish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rainbowmarks.square.site/product/2024-solo-nationals/4&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/august/BlogPostPre/buynow-800-8cffccc6d.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/august/BlogPostPre/buynow-200-8cffccc6d.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/august/BlogPostPre/buynow-400-8cffccc6d.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/august/BlogPostPre/buynow-800-8cffccc6d.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/august/BlogPostPre/buynow-1600-8cffccc6d.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/august/BlogPostPre/buynow-2000-8cffccc6d.jpg 2000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;capturing-every-moment&quot;&gt;Capturing Every Moment&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll be on-site shooting as many competition runs as possible across the four days of the event. Our focus is on action shots that showcase the speed, precision, and thrill of Solo racing. Whether you’re a competitor looking to relive your best runs or a fan wanting to see the action up close, we’ve got you covered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pre-event-special-package-no-longer-available-at-discount&quot;&gt;Pre-Event Special Package (NO LONGER AVAILABLE AT DISCOUNT)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who want comprehensive coverage of their performance, we’re offering an exclusive &lt;strong&gt;Pre-Event Special Package&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$125&lt;/strong&gt; for every one of our published digital photos of your car from the 2024 Solo Nationals. (Individual photos will be $25/photo after the event)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This package includes all photos, no matter how many drivers or classes the car is entered in.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Automatically sorted, tagged and filtered photos for you and your car, no need to “search” through photos after the event.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We’ll be specifically shooting cars that have prepaid! We will guarantee at least 5 individual photos for you (likely many more), or your money back! Everyone else comes second, we may or may not get photos of them!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;25% Discount on any Physical Orders (coupon code will be provided via email after 2024 Solo Nationals galleries are posted)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ProSolo Finale shots can be included for an additional &lt;strong&gt;$50&lt;/strong&gt; even after the Finale!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;to-maximize-our-success-in-capturing-your-car-please-provide-us-with-the-following-details-when-checking-out&quot;&gt;To maximize our success in capturing your car, please provide us with the following details when checking out:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Car number&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Class&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make/Model/Color&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This information helps us focus on your vehicle throughout the event, ensuring we get the best possible shots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can book this package online via &lt;a href=&quot;https://rainbowmarks.square.site/product/2024-solo-nationals/4&quot;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;years-of-solo-nationals-photo-experience&quot;&gt;Years of Solo Nationals Photo Experience&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started attending the Solo Nationals in 2000. Throughout the years I’ve taken thousands upon thousands of competition photos at the event. &lt;a href=&quot;https://flickr.com/search/?user_id=17726343%40N00&amp;amp;view_all=1&amp;amp;text=nationals&quot;&gt;Check out some of the past years work in our Flickr Galleries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;post-event-photo-availability&quot;&gt;Post-Event Photo Availability&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you decide to purchase photos after the event, individual photos will be available for &lt;strong&gt;$25/photo&lt;/strong&gt;. However, securing the pre-event package guarantees you receive all available photos at a significant discount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;important-note&quot;&gt;Important Note&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of right now, we will be running and working the final heat each day, which may limit our ability to shoot cars competing in those classes. We’ll do our best to capture as much as we can, but please be aware of this potential limitation. If you purchase and we don’t get any shots of you, a refund can be given.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;contact-us&quot;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or need to provide us with your car details, feel free to reach out before the event. We’re excited to capture the excitement of Solo Nationals and can’t wait to see you in Lincoln!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned to RainbowMarks Photography for more updates as we get closer to the event. Let’s make this year’s Solo Nationals one to remember!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
    (function(b,d,h,e,f,a,c){a=d.getElementsByTagName(&quot;script&quot;);c=!1;
    var k=e.substring(e.lastIndexOf(&quot;/&quot;)+1);b.formIds=b.formIds?b.formIds:[];
    for(var g=0;g&lt;a.length;g++)-1&lt;a[g].src.indexOf(k)&amp;&amp;(c=!0);b[f]&amp;&amp;(b.formIds=b.formIds.concat(b[f].form_ids));
    b.formObject=f;b[f]=function(a){if(a.form_ids){
        var c=b.formIds.concat(a.form_ids),d=[],e;for(e in c)c.hasOwnProperty(e)&amp;&amp;-1==d.indexOf(c[e])&amp;&amp;d.push(c[e]);
        a.form_ids=d}b[f]=a};c||(a=d.createElement(h),c=d.getElementsByTagName(h)[0],a.async=!0,a.src=e,c.parentNode.insertBefore(a,
            c))})(window,document,&apos;script&apos;, &apos;//cdn3.editmysite.com/app/marketing/js/dist/lead-form.js&apos;,&apos;leadForm&apos;);
    leadForm({ form_ids: [&quot;686236c0-8c5f-4a2f-b962-99e3a83027ea&quot;], preview: 0, asset_domain: &apos;cdn3.editmysite.com/app/marketing&apos;, data_domain: &apos;www.weebly.com/app/marketing&apos; });
&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/08/SoloNationals</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/08/SoloNationals</guid>
        
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>race</category>
        
        <category>car</category>
        
        <category>solo</category>
        
        <category>autocross</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2024 American Water Missouri River 340 Paddle Race</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;📸 2024 American Water Missouri River 340 Photo Galleries Now Available! 📸&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to announce that the photo galleries from the 2024 American Water Missouri River 340 are now available for viewing and purchasing! Dive into the memories and relive the race through our extensive collection of photos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📷 Check out the galleries here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/MR340&quot;&gt;2024 MR340 Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚤 For Pre-Order Customers: Use the Search feature on the gallery by boat number to easily find your photos from the race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔍 For Everyone Else: Over the next few days, I’ll be manually tagging boats I can identify. In the meantime, feel free to browse through the galleries to find your boat. &lt;em&gt;(Update, AI has made an attempt to tag every photo that had a visible number.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔹 Gallery Organization: Photos are organized by location and then broken into rough time windows to make it easier to find your shots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💻 Photo Downloads: The easiest option for getting your race photos is through digital downloads. However, a variety of print formats are also available!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎨 Custom Processing: Want custom processing, cropping, or color adjustments? This service is available for an additional cost and must be handled manually. Please reach out to rainbowmarks@christoc.com for more information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🙏 Thank You: Thank you all for your patience! As a single photographer doing my best to shoot the entire race with very little sleep, if I missed you or your boat, my sincerest apologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for choosing RainbowMarks Photography to capture your 2024 MR340 memories!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best,
Chris Hammond
RainbowMarks Photography
🌈📸&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#MR340 #RainbowMarksPhotography #RacePhotos #Marathon #Kayak #Canoe #Photography #RaceMemories #2024MR340&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/07/MR340/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/07/MR340/</guid>
        
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>race</category>
        
        <category>boat</category>
        
        <category>paddle</category>
        
        <category>MR340</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2024 Miner Tough Weekend</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Year four! of shooting the Miner Tough weekend down in St. Joe State Park here in Missouri kicked off with Trail Run on Saturday July 13th, 2024, followed by the Mountain Bike Race on Sunday July 14th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like last year, the event chose to have our photo services available for everyone to have access to free photo downloads! You can &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Miner-Tough-Weekend&quot;&gt;find the photos from the Miner Tough Weekend events now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll find three different galleries, I tried to get a photo of every entrant but likely missed a few:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Miner-Tough-Weekend/Saturday-Trail-Run&quot;&gt;Trail Run on Saturday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Miner-Tough-Weekend/Sunday-Mountain-Bike-Race&quot;&gt;Mountain Bike Race on Sunday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Miner-Tough-Weekend/Sunday-MTB-GoPro-Randomness&quot;&gt;GoPro random shots from the MTB Race&lt;/a&gt; The camera was sitting next to a tree taking a photo every second. If you happened to pass at the right time to get in the frame and the photo wasn’t the blurriest thing ever created you might find yourself in these.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like you can order prints from our online galleries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big thanks to the event organizers for having us out again this year!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/07/MinerTough/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/07/MinerTough/</guid>
        
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>race</category>
        
        <category>trail</category>
        
        <category>run</category>
        
        <category>mtb</category>
        
        <category>mountain bike</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2024 Big Foot Open House</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the very first blog posts on this website, from back in 2019, was for the &lt;a href=&quot;/Events/2019/09/Big-Foot-Open-House&quot;&gt;2018 Big Foot Open House&lt;/a&gt;. Six years later I finally made it back out to the Big Foot Open House in Pacific Missouri and took more photos!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m fond of High Roller II, so I went with the intention of taking some great pictures of the Krekeler’s Ford Ranger, but I managed to also get quite a few other trucks while I was out there this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the 5 photos I have highlighted here on this blog post, &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/2024-Big-Foot-Open-House&quot;&gt;you can find the full gallery of 154 pictures over here&lt;/a&gt;. As with most of our galleries, you can purchase&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a busy morning with central states hockey tryouts for my boy first thing, after dropping him off at home for a well earned day of rest, I headed south to Pacific. We spend quite a bit of time in Pacific with ice hockey and a couple of meetings with a client from work, but some of the most fun you can have in Pacific is visiting the Big Foot 4x4 Headquarters! I arrived sometime after 11am or so and parking was up to the Walgreens right on the main drag in town. I parked in the first grassy spot I could find and walked down to the open house event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon arrival I dropped off some prints I made for the owner of High Roller II, some of which I will hopefully upgrade with the recent photos taken today!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not long after I arrived Big Foot 15 headed out for a few car crush/jump passes around the fenced off field. I hadn’t really set myself up to get great shots for this first set of runs as the crown was 5 or 6 people deep from the fence when I did manage to walk around to the side of the field. Thankfully I’m tall enough that I was able to shoot over most of the people, and crop out the heads of those I didn’t on the shots of BF15.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After they finished their run most of the crowd cleared out so I moved up to the fence line to make sure I had the angle on the old school car crush that I knew was going to happen soon. My persistance paid off with the shots you can see &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/2024-Big-Foot-Open-House&quot;&gt;in the gallery of 154 shots from today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you attend the Big Foot Open House? What did you think of things this year? The only thing I could suggest, is maybe a water truck next year, put some dampness down on the field and cut down on some of the dust! Now let me go clean my camera off!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you enjoy the old school car crush?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which was your favorite monster truck there this year?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was it the Ford of Big Foot 15? The two dodges, Blue Ox and The Blaine Crusher? What about the lone Chevy Waldo? Or maybe it was one of the Fords,  Old Red Truck, Juggernaut Racing or High Roller II?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/06/big-foot-open-house</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/06/big-foot-open-house</guid>
        
        
        <category>missouri</category>
        
        <category>monster truck</category>
        
        <category>big foot</category>
        
        <category>high roller</category>
        
        <category>events</category>
        
        <category>automobile</category>
        
        <category>trucks</category>
        
        <category>motorsports</category>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>automotive</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spirit of St. Louis Air Show &amp; STEM Expo</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m an Air Force brat, that means I love air shows, so when the Spirit of St. Louis Air Show &amp;amp; STEM Expo come to town every 2 years I am in heaven for the week. I am fortunate enough to live close enough to the airport that I often see performers fly over my house when they arrive and when they are practicing on Thursday and Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week was no different, after getting back from our trip to NYC super early on Thursday morning I was pleasantly notified by my wife around 10am on Thursday that jets were up and flying. I was able to step outside and see the Boeing F-15EX (or was it a QA?) flying over, close enough that I could snap a decent photo with my cell phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent the afternoon Thursday running in and out of the house camera in hand trying to get photos of planes as they flew over while simultaneously trying to get work done throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday I was able to view quite a bit of the practice flights that occurred from up off of Wildhorse Creek road in Chesterfield. Saturday I spent the entire day in a spot at the air show just beyond the end of the runway at Spirit Airport to catch the performers in action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the past 4 days I took nearly thirteen thousand photos, I have spent a considerable amount of time culling down to a manageable list of photos that I thought could be published, you can find over 300 for your viewing pleasure in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Spirit-Of-St-Louis-Air-Show-Stem-Expo&quot;&gt;online gallery&lt;/a&gt; with just a few of those featured in the gallery here on this blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned as we work on some special print discounts from the Air Show later this month.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/06/SpiritOfStLouisAirShow</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/06/SpiritOfStLouisAirShow</guid>
        
        
        <category>missouri</category>
        
        <category>air show</category>
        
        <category>airplanes</category>
        
        <category>blue angels</category>
        
        <category>st louis</category>
        
        <category>fighter</category>
        
        <category>jet</category>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>events</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
