<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RainbowMarks Photography</title>
    <description>RainbowMarks Photography, specializing in event photography in and around St. Louis Missouri.</description>
    <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://rainbowmarks.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:27:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>2024 Big Foot Open House</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the very first blog posts on this website, from back in 2019, was for the &lt;a href=&quot;/Events/2019/09/Big-Foot-Open-House&quot;&gt;2018 Big Foot Open House&lt;/a&gt;. Six years later I finally made it back out to the Big Foot Open House in Pacific Missouri and took more photos!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m fond of High Roller II, so I went with the intention of taking some great pictures of the Krekeler’s Ford Ranger, but I managed to also get quite a few other trucks while I was out there this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the 5 photos I have highlighted here on this blog post, &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/2024-Big-Foot-Open-House&quot;&gt;you can find the full gallery of 154 pictures over here&lt;/a&gt;. As with most of our galleries, you can purchase&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a busy morning with central states hockey tryouts for my boy first thing, after dropping him off at home for a well earned day of rest, I headed south to Pacific. We spend quite a bit of time in Pacific with ice hockey and a couple of meetings with a client from work, but some of the most fun you can have in Pacific is visiting the Big Foot 4x4 Headquarters! I arrived sometime after 11am or so and parking was up to the Walgreens right on the main drag in town. I parked in the first grassy spot I could find and walked down to the open house event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon arrival I dropped off some prints I made for the owner of High Roller II, some of which I will hopefully upgrade with the recent photos taken today!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not long after I arrived Big Foot 15 headed out for a few car crush/jump passes around the fenced off field. I hadn’t really set myself up to get great shots for this first set of runs as the crown was 5 or 6 people deep from the fence when I did manage to walk around to the side of the field. Thankfully I’m tall enough that I was able to shoot over most of the people, and crop out the heads of those I didn’t on the shots of BF15.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After they finished their run most of the crowd cleared out so I moved up to the fence line to make sure I had the angle on the old school car crush that I knew was going to happen soon. My persistance paid off with the shots you can see &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/2024-Big-Foot-Open-House&quot;&gt;in the gallery of 154 shots from today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you attend the Big Foot Open House? What did you think of things this year? The only thing I could suggest, is maybe a water truck next year, put some dampness down on the field and cut down on some of the dust! Now let me go clean my camera off!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you enjoy the old school car crush?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which was your favorite monster truck there this year?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was it the Ford of Big Foot 15? The two dodges, Blue Ox and The Blaine Crusher? What about the lone Chevy Waldo? Or maybe it was one of the Fords,  Old Red Truck, Juggernaut Racing or High Roller II?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/06/big-foot-open-house</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/06/big-foot-open-house</guid>
        
        
        <category>missouri</category>
        
        <category>monster truck</category>
        
        <category>big foot</category>
        
        <category>high roller</category>
        
        <category>events</category>
        
        <category>automobile</category>
        
        <category>trucks</category>
        
        <category>motorsports</category>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>automotive</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spirit of St. Louis Air Show &amp; STEM Expo</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m an Air Force brat, that means I love air shows, so when the Spirit of St. Louis Air Show &amp;amp; STEM Expo come to town every 2 years I am in heaven for the week. I am fortunate enough to live close enough to the airport that I often see performers fly over my house when they arrive and when they are practicing on Thursday and Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week was no different, after getting back from our trip to NYC super early on Thursday morning I was pleasantly notified by my wife around 10am on Thursday that jets were up and flying. I was able to step outside and see the Boeing F-15EX (or was it a QA?) flying over, close enough that I could snap a decent photo with my cell phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent the afternoon Thursday running in and out of the house camera in hand trying to get photos of planes as they flew over while simultaneously trying to get work done throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday I was able to view quite a bit of the practice flights that occurred from up off of Wildhorse Creek road in Chesterfield. Saturday I spent the entire day in a spot at the air show just beyond the end of the runway at Spirit Airport to catch the performers in action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the past 4 days I took nearly thirteen thousand photos, I have spent a considerable amount of time culling down to a manageable list of photos that I thought could be published, you can find over 300 for your viewing pleasure in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Spirit-Of-St-Louis-Air-Show-Stem-Expo&quot;&gt;online gallery&lt;/a&gt; with just a few of those featured in the gallery here on this blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned as we work on some special print discounts from the Air Show later this month.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/06/SpiritOfStLouisAirShow</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/06/SpiritOfStLouisAirShow</guid>
        
        
        <category>missouri</category>
        
        <category>air show</category>
        
        <category>airplanes</category>
        
        <category>blue angels</category>
        
        <category>st louis</category>
        
        <category>fighter</category>
        
        <category>jet</category>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>events</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>St. Louis Region Autocross Photos 2024</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the home of St. Louis Region Autocross Photos for the 2024 Season from RainbowMarks Photography. We’ll be updating this post with galleries from each event we cover during the 2024 Season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;event-2&quot;&gt;Event #2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first event was Event #2 on April 21, 2024 at the Family Arena in St. Charles, Missouri. &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Autocross/St-Louis-Region-SCCA/4-21-2024-Event-2/Heat-3&quot;&gt;We shot the Third Heat of the event and posted 300+ pictures in our online gallery&lt;/a&gt;, a few of which are featured here on this page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Autocross/St-Louis-Region-SCCA/4-21-2024-Event-2/Heat-3&quot;&gt;View Event #2 Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also be sure to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.autocrossblog.com/st-louis-autocross-event-2-2024&quot;&gt;check out the event writeup on AutocrossBlog.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;event-3-cam-challenge&quot;&gt;Event #3 CAM Challenge&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next event in the series was the CAM Challenge event held May 4th and 5th at the St. Charles Family Arena. We shot both Heat 2 and Heat 3 over Saturday afternoon and Sunday morning. 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Autocross/STL-CAM-Challenge&quot;&gt;View Event #3 Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also be sure to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.autocrossblog.com/2024-st-louis-cam-challenge&quot;&gt;check out the event writeup on AutocrossBlog.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/04/StLouisRegion</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/04/StLouisRegion</guid>
        
        
        <category>missouri</category>
        
        <category>cars</category>
        
        <category>autocross</category>
        
        <category>st louis</category>
        
        <category>scca</category>
        
        <category>automotive</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>April 8th 2024 Eclipse from Trail of Tears State Park in Jackson, Missouri</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After experiencing the Total Eclipse passing over our home in Wildwood Missouri in 2017, we vowed as a family we would watch the next one together! For the 2017 event our oldest daughter was at school that day, maybe 1/2 mile away, but not with us. For the 2024 Eclipse we pulled both kids from school and hit the road just after 7am to head towards the path of totality. I was fearful of crazy traffic, but we left early enough that we avoided the morning chaos that would follow on I-55 southbound from St. Louis later in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;finding-a-place-to-watch-the-eclipse&quot;&gt;Finding a place to watch the eclipse&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent a few evenings trying to determine where to watch the eclipse from. I had a couple of criteria when searching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As much totality as possible: We were lucky that within a 2 hours drive south or east, we could find locations in the path of totality that had over 4 minutes of time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clear skies: Both for weather and line of sight to the sun. There are a lot of places in Missouri where the sun can be blocked by the trees, finding a clear line of sight was important.
Sunday the 7th I spent a few hours pouring over potential locations and weather forecasts. I did something similar in 2017, waking up a few times early in the morning trying to scout out locations with the best chance of no cloud cover, ultimately based on forecasts, we stayed home, making the right choice. For 2024 this wasn’t going to be an option, our house wasn’t in the path of totality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday evening I decided that Trail of Tears State Park outside of Jackson, MO would likely be our best choice, but I had a backup option of driving to a friend’s house in Illinois if something went wrong with the state park choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting down to the state park was relatively uneventful, morning traffic in St. Louis wasn’t too bad, though it did start to back up just before Festus going south, for what I believe was construction. We ended up hopping off the highway and taking 61 for about 8 miles before getting back on I-55 south. Other folks who left an hour or two later had a nightmare of non-stop traffic all the way south on I-55. We ended up getting to the park just before 10am and were able to find what I would estimate to be one of the final 20 spots available at the time. We parked down near the boatramp, which was perfect for us because our son was excited about fishing for a while in the Mississippi river while waiting for the eclipse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;getting-setup&quot;&gt;Getting setup&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We ended up deciding to watch the eclipse from right near our parked truck as opposed to finding a grassy spot to sit in. I wanted to keep our clear sky view and not have any trees blocking our view or any of the cameras I would be setting up. We packed lunch and snacks ahead of time, so beyond fishing and hitting the public restrooms we didn’t need to leave our spot for anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;equipment&quot;&gt;Equipment&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the eclipse I would be shooting with 3 cameras, though only one really counted. I setup two GoPro cameras on tripods, one a Hero12 set to record video for the entirety of the eclipse. The other a Hero9 that I set on a timelapse, taking a photo every 5 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My main rig for shooting the eclipse was my &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/43YUB1K&quot;&gt;Canon R5&lt;/a&gt;. For a lens I had a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3JkqUPh&quot;&gt;70-200m&lt;/a&gt; and a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3W01HkS&quot;&gt;2X extender&lt;/a&gt; attached. I attached a solar filter (same one I used in 2017) to the lens hood with rubberbands, this allowed me to quickly remove the filter during totality to get unprotected shots of the eclipse. The filter I used was an &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3vKdhG2&quot;&gt;8” Orion filter, though not as fancy as the ones currently on Amazon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All three cameras were mounted on their own tripod, though none of them with any star trackers, maybe in the future I’ll have one of those fancy tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/eclipse/Equipment-1-800-42ac113f9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Eclipse Photo Camera Setup&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/eclipse/Equipment-1-200-42ac113f9.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/eclipse/Equipment-1-400-42ac113f9.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/eclipse/Equipment-1-800-42ac113f9.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/eclipse/Equipment-1-1600-42ac113f9.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/eclipse/Equipment-1-2000-42ac113f9.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;during-the-eclipse&quot;&gt;During the Eclipse&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the event I was running back and forth between my R5 and the family. Trying to get a variety of shots, but also trying to spend time with the family as well. I had my camera setup on shutter priority (TV), which means I was targetting adjustment of primarily the shutterspeed for the event. I shot a variety of speeds from 1/5 (of a second) up to 1/8000, though a majority of the shots and what worked were between 1/640 and 1/2500. For my ISO I shot at 100 pretty much the entire time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest struggle I had during the eclipse was focusing. I tried setting auto-focus to on but for that to work you always have to be centered on the sun, and that’s very difficult to do when running on a tripod with a long lens/extender. You don’t realize how quickly the sun moves until you watch it though a zoom. So for focusing I manually focused, though the real struggle there was the solar filter. The way I had it mounted on the lens hood (without the hood extended) meant getting to the focus ring with my large hands was difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ended up working with focus throughout the day, though I am not sure I was ever 100% happy with how I got it set, for the most part the photos worked out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;see-and-purchase-the-results&quot;&gt;See and Purchase The Results&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now for the important part, the actual results! You can find the photos I have processed and chosen to post here on the page, &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/April-8th-2024-Total-Eclipse&quot;&gt;as well as in our high resolution gallery available here&lt;/a&gt;. Most of the shots I’ve posted are during totality, though I have quite a few other stages. Bluntly, the other stages of the eclipse sort of get repetitive, while they make cool composition shots, I found them boring as individual shots so I didn’t post them for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll find in the shots a couple of composites, where I merged together multiple photos to create something unique. &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/April-8th-2024-Total-Eclipse&quot;&gt;All of these photos are available as prints, canvas and acrylics via our online gallery&lt;/a&gt;. If you’re interested in purchasing one of these photos in another format, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/Contact&quot;&gt;please feel free to reach out&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;you-need-to-experience-a-total-eclipse&quot;&gt;You need to experience a Total Eclipse!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experiencing a Total Eclipse is a profound, almost mystical event. While a partial eclipse is certainly memorable, achieving totality transforms the experience entirely. It’s something you truly have to see for yourself to understand the full emotional and visual impact. People travel thousands of miles for just a few minutes of this celestial phenomenon, and once you’ve witnessed it, you’ll understand why. To get a taste of what I’m talking about, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HqN1OctY_30&quot;&gt;check out this captivating 7-minute, 4K video of the eclipse&lt;/a&gt;. Totality starts around 1:16, and you can hear the awe and excitement in the crowd’s reactions. It’s a preview of the exhilarating experience that awaits you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;give-your-feedback&quot;&gt;Give your feedback!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any feedback on our eclipse photos, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/rainbowmarksphoto&quot;&gt;feel free to follow along and comment on our photos over on our Facebook page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;upcoming-eclipses-start-planning&quot;&gt;Upcoming Eclipses! Start Planning!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the total solar eclipse on April 8, 2024, the next five total solar eclipses will be:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;August 12, 2026&lt;/strong&gt;: Visible in northern North America, western Africa, and Europe.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;August 2, 2027&lt;/strong&gt;: Visible in Africa, Europe, the Middle East, western and southern Asia.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;July 22, 2028&lt;/strong&gt;: Visible in Southeast Asia, the East Indies, Australia, and New Zealand.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;November 25, 2030&lt;/strong&gt;: Visible in southern Africa, the southern Indian Ocean, the East Indies, Australia, and Antarctica.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 30, 2033&lt;/strong&gt;: Visible in western Europe, northern Asia, North America, the Pacific, the Atlantic, and the Arctic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/04/Eclipse</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/04/Eclipse</guid>
        
        
        <category>space</category>
        
        <category>eclipse</category>
        
        <category>sun</category>
        
        <category>moon</category>
        
        <category>totality</category>
        
        <category>missouri</category>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NASA PACE Falcon 9 Rocket Launch</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In February of 2024, I had the pleasure of spending some time in Florida for a work conference. While there, I kept an eye on the forecast and space launch schedule to see if I might catch a rocket launch while in town. SpaceX was planning to launch a Falcon 9 with the NASA PACE payload. The launch ended up being delayed for 3 days, finally happening early in the morning on February 8th, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was not a publicly accessible launch, and I’m not sure why, but my assumption is that Falcon 9 launches are getting so frequent nowadays that late night/early morning launches are too much work from an organization perspective to try to allow the public access to the Cape to see launches. So, what does this mean? The public can still watch; they just have to do it from remote locations, not on the Cape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-800-d92b355ad.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mission Control Morrell Operations Center Entry&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-200-d92b355ad.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-400-d92b355ad.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-800-d92b355ad.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-1600-d92b355ad.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-0-2000-d92b355ad.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-800-d20ce17ef.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mission Control Morrell Operations Center Display&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-200-d20ce17ef.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-400-d20ce17ef.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-800-d20ce17ef.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-1600-d20ce17ef.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-1-2000-d20ce17ef.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where did I watch the launch? I was fortunate enough to be invited to join a couple of remote family members who live and even work on the Cape, so I got special access. The morning started out with a quick tour of Mission Control, yes, Mission Control for the launch! There are actually two different rooms for MC, one for the active launch, and one for anything else going on or tours, so we got to walk through the empty mission control room and look into the active room. With Falcon 9 launches, the number of people in mission control is pretty minimal, which was surprising to see considering what was occurring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-800-77caf8f5b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mission Control at Morrell Operations Center with Me!&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-200-77caf8f5b.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-400-77caf8f5b.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-800-77caf8f5b.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-1600-77caf8f5b.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-2-2000-77caf8f5b.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-800-22a541a5e.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mission Control at Morrell Operations Center&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-200-22a541a5e.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-400-22a541a5e.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-800-22a541a5e.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-1600-22a541a5e.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-3-2000-22a541a5e.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was the best part about the Mission Control tour? The laugh I got in the bathroom! Check out this sign. If the people who are launching rockets into space can’t even hit the toilet, how are they going to land on Mars? (sorry, I couldn’t resist)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-800-93b5aef0b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mission Control Urinals&quot; srcset=&quot;/generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-200-93b5aef0b.jpg 200w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-400-93b5aef0b.jpg 400w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-800-93b5aef0b.jpg 800w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-1600-93b5aef0b.jpg 1600w, /generated/img/posts/2024/space/nasapace/MissionControl-4-2000-93b5aef0b.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then came the launch itself. I won’t share exact details on where we were for the launch, but boy was that an experience! This Falcon 9 rocket was launching towards the south, something that a NASA payload hadn’t done in 50+ years, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thor-Ablestar&quot;&gt;the last time on November 30th, 1960, having a problem during launch and rumored to kill a cow in Cuba&lt;/a&gt;. After the launch, and I mean, almost right after, like 7 minutes, the rocket would come back and land also on the Cape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were set up to watch the launch, knowing that we didn’t have the best spot to view the landing pad, but had thoughts of maybe trying to drive over to catch the landing. Long story short, we didn’t make it over to see the landing, we took too long watching the launch and nearly missed the landing altogether as we were driving west towards it when the sky lit up with what looked like lightning then the sun as the rocket reignited for landing along with sonic booms as it broke the sound barrier. I managed to stick the camera out the window of the SUV and got a shot or two, but nothing great of the landing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a great experience, it had been 14 years since I saw my first shuttle launch, also a night launch with access to the Cape from an employee. This launch had a little less excitement as the Shuttle launch we had to rush to get on the bus to depart our viewing location because of the risk of an acid cloud blowing back at us!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t wait for my next launch, and definitely am taking my family with me next time so they can experience it too!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/03/NASAPACELaunch</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/03/NASAPACELaunch</guid>
        
        
        <category>space</category>
        
        <category>rocket</category>
        
        <category>launch</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2024 Blue Note Cup Photos</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;-book-your-game-today&quot;&gt;📸 Book Your Game Today!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At RainbowMarks Photography, we’re thrilled to announce our exclusive photography services for the Blue Note Cup 2024! Get ready to immortalize your team’s moments of glory on the ice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;exclusive-offer-225game&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exclusive Offer: $225/Game&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Must book by 3/1/2024) For just $225, secure a spot on our shooting schedule and ensure your game is captured through our lenses with precision and creativity. But that’s not all - your booking grants you:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professionally Processed Photos:&lt;/strong&gt; After the game, access and download the high-quality, professionally processed images of your game directly from our website.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10% Off Physical Prints:&lt;/strong&gt; Dive into your game’s photo gallery online and order physical prints to keep those memories tangible. Enjoy a 10% discount on every print, turning moments into lasting mementos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-choose-rainbowmarks-photography&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Choose RainbowMarks Photography?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on Your Team:&lt;/strong&gt; By booking ahead, you guarantee that we capture the essence of your team’s performance, focusing on the moments that matter most to you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High-Quality Imagery:&lt;/strong&gt; With RainbowMarks Photography, expect nothing less than professional-grade photos that capture the intensity, emotion, and triumph of your games.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easy Access &amp;amp; Ordering:&lt;/strong&gt; After the game, effortlessly download your photos and order prints from the convenience of your home.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;booking-is-essential&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Booking Is Essential!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, to ensure we cover your game and concentrate on your team, &lt;strong&gt;advance booking is necessary&lt;/strong&gt;. Spots fill up fast, especially for an event as anticipated as the Blue Note Cup 2024. Any bookings after 3/1/2024 are $300/game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;capture-the-moment-relive-the-glory&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capture the Moment, Relive the Glory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t let these fleeting moments slip away. Book RainbowMarks Photography now and keep the spirit of the game alive through stunning photographs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📅 &lt;strong&gt;Schedule Your Game:&lt;/strong&gt; Contact us today (650)260-8344 to secure your booking and take the first step towards capturing the heart and soul of your team’s journey at the Blue Note Cup 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/02/BlueNoteCupPhotography</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/02/BlueNoteCupPhotography</guid>
        
        
        <category>hockey</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bald Eagles in Clarksville, Missouri January 2024</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On Sunday morning, the 21st of January, I headed up to Clarksville Missouri to look for Bald Eagles along the Mississippi River.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I arrived just after sunrise (next time I’ll leave earlier) and immediately saw two Bald Eagles flying just north of the lock and dam. I knew it was going to be a good day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I parked in the public parking near the lock and dam and immediately started getting my equipment ready to get setup. I took a monopod, instead of a tripod for the day, though I am not sure if that was the best choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other photographers who were there had tripods, while I had a little more mobility than they did, I feel like I could have used the stability of a tripod. I’ll have to try that next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a rather cold morning, and while I thought I was prepared for the chill, I wasn’t. Next time I’ll go I’ll be sure to take a mask and better gloves with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Eagles south of the damn were pretty active just after sunrise, with bursts of activity as they were trying to find fish in the river.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After an hour or so in Clarksville, I headed south on 79. I ended up driving through Clarence Cannon National Wildlife Refuge. I also stopped for a bit in Winfield, Missouri and found a few more Bald Eagles hunting there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here in the gallery you can see a couple of the shots I was able to capture, I look forward to going back again soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve posted a 36 megabyte image that has 99 shots of one particular Bald Eagle going through the motions of catching and flying off with a fish. You can see the full high resolution photo here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://rainbowmarks.com/img/Birds2024-2.jpg&quot;&gt;Bald Eagle Catching Fish&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/BaldEaglesClarksville</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/BaldEaglesClarksville</guid>
        
        
        <category>wildlife</category>
        
        <category>nature</category>
        
        <category>bald eagles</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>January 20th weekend Hockey!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Chesterfield Falcons had two games the weekend of January 20th, 2024. The AI generated game summaries are below!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-summary-chesterfield-falcons-10ua1-vs-kirkwood-stars-10ua1&quot;&gt;Game Summary: Chesterfield Falcons 10UA1 vs Kirkwood Stars 10UA1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;location-maryville-university-hockey-center-shanahan-rink&quot;&gt;Location: Maryville University Hockey Center, Shanahan Rink&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;date-saturday-january-20th-2024&quot;&gt;Date: Saturday January 20th, 2024&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an exhilarating display of youth ice hockey, the Chesterfield Falcons 10UA1 faced off against the Kirkwood Stars 10UA1 at the Maryville University Hockey Center on the Shanahan rink. The matchup was highly anticipated, especially considering the history of the two teams. In their previous encounters, the Kirkwood Stars had dominated, winning 10-2 and 7-0. However, this game proved to be a stark contrast to their past meetings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the drop of the puck, it was evident that the Falcons had come with a new level of determination and skill. Both teams exhibited remarkable talent and teamwork, making it a thrilling game to watch. The Falcons, showing significant improvement from their previous games, matched the Stars play for play, leading to a nail-bitingly close contest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the game, the lead oscillated between the two teams, with each side scoring impressive goals. The young athletes on the ice demonstrated not only skill but also sportsmanship and a passion for the game, which was infectious for the audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the final buzzer sounded, the scoreboard read 6-6, marking the end of regulation time in a draw. This result was a testament to the hard work and improvement of the Chesterfield Falcons, who managed to hold their own against a team that had previously bested them with significant margins. For the Kirkwood Stars, it was a reminder of the unpredictability and competitive spirit inherent in sports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, this game was not just a display of young talent, but also a story of resilience, improvement, and the unyielding spirit of competition. Both the Chesterfield Falcons and the Kirkwood Stars should be proud of their performance in a game that will surely be remembered for its intensity and the remarkable skill displayed by all players involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-summary-chesterfield-falcons-10ua1-vs-affton-all-americans-10ua1&quot;&gt;Game Summary: Chesterfield Falcons 10UA1 vs Affton All-Americans 10UA1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;location-maryville-university-hockey-center-shanahan-rink-1&quot;&gt;Location: Maryville University Hockey Center, Shanahan Rink&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;date-sunday-january-21st-2024&quot;&gt;Date: Sunday January 21st, 2024&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Chesterfield Falcons 10UA1 continued their impressive run in youth ice hockey with a solid victory over the Affton All-Americans 10UA1, finishing with a score of 4-1. This game, held at the same rink where they had tied the day before with another team, showcased the Falcons’ resilience and skill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Affton All-Americans started the game on a high note, with Chase Cotton opening the scoring with 6:55 left in the first period. This early lead set the stage for an intense game, but the Falcons quickly responded. Demonstrating their competitive spirit and ability to handle pressure, Chesterfield’s defenseman Matthew Pitcher tied the game just 1:10 later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Falcons’ momentum continued to build as Bennett Suda attempted to dump the puck in front of the goal, leading to an unexpected but welcome goal, putting Chesterfield in the lead. The first period ended with the Falcons leading 2-1, a testament to their quick recovery and offensive prowess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the second period, the Falcons maintained their dominance. Levi James extended their lead with a goal with 5:59 remaining, showcasing the depth of talent in the Chesterfield team. The Falcons’ defense and goaltender also deserve commendation for their performance in keeping the All-Americans at bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third period saw Chesterfield solidifying their lead. Bennett Suda, assisted by Lucky Huntebrinker, scored with 6:54 remaining, bringing the score to 4-1. This goal underscored the Falcons’ strategic play and effective teamwork throughout the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The final whistle confirmed Chesterfield’s victory, with a repeat scoreline of 4-1 against the Affton All-Americans, similar to their previous encounter. This win further established the Falcons as a formidable team in the league, capable of maintaining consistency and showcasing improvement game after game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the Affton All-Americans, despite the loss, the team’s early goal and overall performance highlighted their potential and the competitive nature of the league. Both teams exhibited commendable skill and sportsmanship, making it an enjoyable game for spectators and a valuable experience for the young athletes involved.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/January20thHockey</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/January20thHockey</guid>
        
        
        <category>events</category>
        
        <category>hockey</category>
        
        <category>games</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Book Your 2024 Events with RainbowMarks Photography – Capture Every Moment!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you planning an event in 2024 around Wildwood, Missouri, or in the broader St. Louis area? Looking for a professional photography service that captures the essence of your special moments? Look no further than &lt;strong&gt;RainbowMarks Photography&lt;/strong&gt;, a leader in &lt;strong&gt;event photography in Wildwood, MO&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;capturing-the-spirit-of-the-midwest&quot;&gt;Capturing the Spirit of the Midwest&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While based in Wildwood, our lenses capture events far and wide across the Midwest. RainbowMarks Photography is not only a top choice in &lt;strong&gt;professional photography in St. Louis&lt;/strong&gt;, but also across the region. We’ve covered a diverse range of events, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The 2023 MR340 Paddle Race on the Missouri River, showcasing our skill in &lt;a href=&quot;https://rainbowmarks.com/MR340/2023/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Missouri River paddle race photos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The action-packed Miner Tough weekend with running and mountain biking events, highlighting our expertise in &lt;strong&gt;sports event photography&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Unbound Gravel race in Emporia, Kansas, where we delivered stunning &lt;strong&gt;Unbound Gravel Emporia, KS photography&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our cameras are adept at capturing the spirit of these dynamic events, and we’re eager to bring the same energy and professionalism to your occasion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;specialized-sports-event-photography&quot;&gt;Specialized Sports Event Photography&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At RainbowMarks Photography, we understand the dynamics of various sports. That’s why we offer specialized photography services for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Baseball&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Football&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hockey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lacrosse&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Field Hockey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Soccer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Auto Racing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And many more sports! Whether it’s a fast-paced hockey game or strategic soccer plays, our photographers excel in capturing every pivotal moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;flexible-photography-packages&quot;&gt;Flexible Photography Packages&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding the diverse needs of different events, we offer various packages:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Daily rates for comprehensive coverage.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weekend packages for extended events.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rates for individual games or matches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;beyond-digital-images&quot;&gt;Beyond Digital Images&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Choose from a range of photo products:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;High-quality digital images for download or purchase.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hard copy prints.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Large canvas and vinyl prints for impactful displays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;book-early-for-2024&quot;&gt;Book Early for 2024!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 calendar fills up, we encourage early bookings, especially for weekends. [Contact us for &lt;strong&gt;Midwest event photography packages&lt;/strong&gt; and pricing details]](https://www.chrishammond.com/Contact).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RainbowMarks Photography&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Event Photography in Wildwood, MO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Serving St. Louis and the Midwest&lt;br /&gt;
“Capturing Every Moment with Color and Passion”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/Contact&quot;&gt;Book Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/&quot;&gt;Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/rainbowmarksphoto&quot;&gt;Like us on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📞 Contact us today to discuss your event needs and let us help you preserve your memories in vivid detail. Remember, the best moments are fleeting, but our photographs make them last forever!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/BookYour2024Events</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2024/01/BookYour2024Events</guid>
        
        
        <category>events</category>
        
        <category>bookings</category>
        
        <category>book</category>
        
        <category>digital</category>
        
        <category>downloads</category>
        
        <category>packages</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Pricing! 30% reduction in price on most physical items!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming into 2024, we’re making some changes! We’ve reduced our pricing for physical items (prints, frames, metal, acrylic, canvas, mugs, etc.) by up to 30%! We plan to keep these prices for the foreseeable future!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;get-ordering&quot;&gt;Get Ordering!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find all our photos from the last couple of years available for purchase in our &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/&quot;&gt;Galleries&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-digital-pricing-and-offering&quot;&gt;New Digital Pricing and Offering&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re offering a lower-resolution digital download that you can use on social media for $10. At this time, we will no longer be offering high-resolution digital downloads of our work except for special occasions and prepaid events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope you enjoy our work, and we look forward to seeing you at an event soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;planning-an-event-in-2024&quot;&gt;Planning an event in 2024?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re booking now for 2024! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/Contact&quot;&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt; today! Reach out early and get discounted event pricing!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/12/HolidayPrices</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/12/HolidayPrices</guid>
        
        
        <category>sale</category>
        
        <category>holiday</category>
        
        <category>christmas</category>
        
        <category>prints</category>
        
        <category>physical</category>
        
        <category>digital</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
