<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RainbowMarks Photography</title>
    <description>RainbowMarks Photography, Wildwood, Missouri</description>
    <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://rainbowmarks.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 21:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 21:05:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>MO Judges Cup Gymnastics - November 10, 2023</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Photos from Olympia Ellisville Xcel Silver competing at the MO Judges Cup 2023 Gymnastics Competition at the Olympia Manchester facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Gymnastics/MO-Judges-Cup-2023&quot;&gt;Click here to View the Full Gallery and / Purchase Photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/frame/slideshow?key=MXwxM2&amp;amp;speed=3&amp;amp;transition=fade&amp;amp;autoStart=1&amp;amp;captions=0&amp;amp;navigation=0&amp;amp;playButton=0&amp;amp;randomize=0&amp;amp;transitionSpeed=2&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/11/MoJudgesCup</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/11/MoJudgesCup</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>gymnastics</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chesterfield Falcons 10U-A1 Shine at the Leprechaun Lashout Tournament</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Chesterfield Falcons 10U-A1 team showcased their talent and determination at the prestigious Leprechaun Lashout tournament held at the iconic Notre Dame University. Here’s a recap of their journey game by game:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-1-chesterfield-falcons-vs-chicago-flames&quot;&gt;Game 1: Chesterfield Falcons vs. Chicago Flames&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the tournament’s opening game held at the Ice Box, the Falcons asserted their dominance early on. &lt;strong&gt;Daniel Hammond&lt;/strong&gt; spearheaded the charge with the opening goal, setting the tone for the rest of the game. Although the official scoreboard showcased an impressive 8-0 win, sources say the Falcons had notched up at least 12 goals! &lt;strong&gt;Braxton Vatterott&lt;/strong&gt; was particularly scintillating, with a hattrick under his belt. Adding another feather to their cap, &lt;strong&gt;Miles McCarthy&lt;/strong&gt; recorded his first shutout of the season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-2-chesterfield-falcons-vs-joliet-jaguars&quot;&gt;Game 2: Chesterfield Falcons vs. Joliet Jaguars&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning’s clash with the Joliet Jaguars Squirt 1 team on the “Lefty Smith” rink proved to be a challenging one for the Falcons. The Jaguars’ strategy of utilizing breakaways put them in the driver’s seat, ultimately clinching a 7-3 victory. Despite the loss, the Falcons learned valuable lessons in teamwork and resilience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-3-chesterfield-falcons-vs-fox-motors-hockey-club&quot;&gt;Game 3: Chesterfield Falcons vs. Fox Motors Hockey Club&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bouncing back from the morning’s setback, the Falcons were in splendid form against the Fox Motors Hockey Club on Notre Dame’s Olympic rink. Securing a comfortable 5-2 victory, the win was a testament to the team’s fighting spirit. Although they conceded two late goals, the Falcons’ performance ensured their place in the championship showdown. The victory was made even sweeter with a memorable team photo session at the Compton Family Ice Arena.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;championship-game-chesterfield-falcons-vs-joliet-jaguars&quot;&gt;Championship Game: Chesterfield Falcons vs. Joliet Jaguars&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday morning brought with it the promise of redemption as the Falcons once again faced the Jaguars. Although the Jaguars took the early lead, it was &lt;strong&gt;Daniel “Hammer” Hammond&lt;/strong&gt; who dazzled with his finesse, tying the game with a remarkable goal. The momentum swung in the Falcons’ favor when &lt;strong&gt;Bennett Suda&lt;/strong&gt; found the net, giving them a lead they wouldn’t relinquish. &lt;strong&gt;Jasper Boyher&lt;/strong&gt; put the cherry on top with a late empty-netter, ensuring the Falcons clinched the Squirt AA title of the Leprechaun Lashout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;in-conclusion&quot;&gt;In Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Leprechaun Lashout tournament was a testament to the Chesterfield Falcons 10U-A1 team’s skill, determination, and heart. They fought, they learned, and they emerged victorious. Kudos to every player, coach, and supporter for this remarkable achievement!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Hockey/23-24-Falcons-10U-A1/Leprechaun-Lashout&quot;&gt;View the full gallery with 600+ photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/11/leprechaunlashout/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/11/leprechaunlashout/</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>hockey</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Affton Americans Youth Ice Hockey Photos - 10U-A1 10-8-2023</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Summary: Affton Americans vs. Chesterfield Falcons (10U A1 Squirt Hockey Match on 10/8/2023)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Hockey/23-24-Falcons-10U-A1/10-8-2023-vs-Affton-Americans&quot;&gt;View the full gallery with 160+ photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an exciting clash between the Affton Americans and the Chesterfield Falcons, the Falcons soared to victory, securing their first win of the season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Details&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teams&lt;/strong&gt;: Affton Americans (Home) vs. Chesterfield Falcons (Visiting)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Score&lt;/strong&gt;: Affton Americans 2 - 5 Chesterfield Falcons&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scoring by Periods&lt;/strong&gt;:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;1st Period: Affton Americans 0 - Chesterfield Falcons 2&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;2nd Period: Affton Americans 2 - Chesterfield Falcons 2&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;3rd Period: Affton Americans 0 - Chesterfield Falcons 1&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shots on Goal&lt;/strong&gt;:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Affton Americans: 1st Period (6), 2nd Period (4), 3rd Period (7), Total (17)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Chesterfield Falcons: 1st Period (6), 2nd Period (11), 3rd Period (4), Total (21)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Goal Scorers&lt;/strong&gt;:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Chesterfield Falcons: Huntebrinker, Sciarratta, Ryan Pitcher, and Jackson Franklin.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Affton Americans: Scoring details not specified.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both teams displayed a commendable performance on the rink. Chesterfield’s Huntebrinker, Sciarratta, Ryan Pitcher, and Jackson Franklin played a pivotal role in their team’s success, each finding the back of the net. The Falcons were consistent in their goal-scoring across all periods, while the Americans made a strong comeback in the second period, only to be held scoreless in the third.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to the Chesterfield Falcons for achieving their first victory of the season. Both teams showcased great skill and sportsmanship, making it an engaging watch for all spectators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Hockey/23-24-Falcons-10U-A1/10-8-2023-vs-Affton-Americans&quot;&gt;View the full gallery with 160+ photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested in having your team’s ice hockey game photographed? &lt;a href=&quot;/events/hockey/&quot;&gt;Read more about our Ice Hockey Photo packages&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/10/AfftonAmericansIceHockeyPhotos/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/10/AfftonAmericansIceHockeyPhotos/</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>hockey</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>St. Peters Youth Ice Hockey Photos - 10U-A1 10-7-2023</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-summary-st-peters-hockey-vs-chesterfield-falcons-10u-a1-squirt-hockey-match&quot;&gt;Game Summary: St. Peters Hockey vs Chesterfield Falcons (10U A1 Squirt Hockey Match)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Hockey/23-24-Falcons-10U-A1/10-7-2023-vs-St-Peters&quot;&gt;View the full gallery with 170+ photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an electrifying matchup between St. Peters Hockey and Chesterfield Falcons, fans were treated to a display of talent, grit, and determination from both squads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game was set into motion with St. Peters taking an early lead, ending the first period 4-2. Despite the initial advantage, Chesterfield’s standout player, Suda, demonstrated his skill, accounting for all three of the team’s initial goals, including one in the second period. This brought the score to 5-3 in favor of St. Peters as they headed into the final period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the third period wound down, tension reached its peak. Chesterfield, showing their never-say-die spirit, managed to pull the score within one, trailing 6-5. In a tactical move, Chesterfield decided to pull their goalie, allowing an extra skater onto the ice. This strategy is commonly used to increase offensive pressure in hopes of equalizing the score. However, due to an oversight by the referees who mistakenly believed Chesterfield had too many players on the ice, a potential game-tying scoring opportunity was thwarted. This error in judgment shifted the momentum, hindering Chesterfield’s chances of leveling the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite their best efforts, the Chesterfield Falcons were unable to recapture their momentum, culminating in a hard-fought 6-5 victory for St. Peters Hockey. Both teams displayed tremendous heart and skill, making it a memorable game for all in attendance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Hockey/23-24-Falcons-10U-A1/10-7-2023-vs-St-Peters&quot;&gt;View the full gallery with 170+ photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested in having your team’s ice hockey game photographed? &lt;a href=&quot;/events/hockey/&quot;&gt;Read more about our Ice Hockey Photo packages&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/10/StPetersIceHockeyPhotos/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/10/StPetersIceHockeyPhotos/</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>hockey</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Capturing the Spirit of CrossFit Competitions in St. Louis</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to RainbowMarks Photography, where passion meets prowess! If you’re seeking exceptional photography that vibrates with the spirit and intensity of CrossFit competitions, then you’re in the right place. We’ve been at the heart of the action, capturing athletes in their finest moments, defying gravity and showcasing the very essence of determination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;experience-matters&quot;&gt;Experience Matters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our commitment to perfection is evident in every snap we take. Over the years, RainbowMarks Photography has become a trusted name in event photography, especially within the robust and growing community of CrossFit enthusiasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌟 &lt;strong&gt;Highlight: CrossFit Games 2019&lt;/strong&gt; 🌟&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RainbowMarks was honored to have been present at the epicenter of the CrossFit world - the &lt;strong&gt;CrossFit Games in 2019&lt;/strong&gt;. Our lenses caught the grit, the sweat, the tears, and the euphoria. It’s one thing to witness these moments live, but through our pictures, we make them timeless. The dynamism of every lift, jump, and sprint was immortalized in our frames, creating memories that participants and fans can cherish forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;local-legends&quot;&gt;Local Legends&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While international events like the CrossFit Games remain a highlight, our heart beats close to home. We’ve been a prominent part of multiple events in and around &lt;strong&gt;St. Louis&lt;/strong&gt; and have traversed across &lt;strong&gt;Missouri&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Illinois&lt;/strong&gt; to bring the magic of CrossFit competitions to life. We understand the local ethos, the vibrant community spirit, and the undying commitment of athletes. That’s why we are a favorite amongst event organizers and participants alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-choose-rainbowmarks&quot;&gt;Why Choose RainbowMarks?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expertise&lt;/strong&gt;: Our experience in photographing CrossFit events is unparalleled. We know the best angles, moments, and techniques to ensure every shot is iconic.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Passion&lt;/strong&gt;: For us, photography isn’t just a job – it’s a love affair with the art of capturing moments. Our passion for CrossFit and our dedication to photography merge to create extraordinary results.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Commitment&lt;/strong&gt;: We are committed to our craft and to our clients. Every event is a new story, and we ensure it’s told in the most captivating way.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Local Understanding&lt;/strong&gt;: Being deeply rooted in Missouri and St. Louis, we have a unique understanding of the local spirit, ensuring that every photo resonates with familiarity and warmth.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;join-us-on-a-photographic-journey&quot;&gt;Join Us on a Photographic Journey&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re an event organizer, a CrossFit athlete, or a fan, we invite you to experience the world through our lens. Let RainbowMarks Photography be the bridge between your event and unforgettable memories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For inquiries, bookings, or to simply ask a question, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/Contact&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, with RainbowMarks, every shot is not just a photo; it’s an emotion, a memory, a legacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/Contact&quot;&gt;Book Today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/10/CrossFitPhotography/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/10/CrossFitPhotography/</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>CrossFit</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Side Hustle at Sky Music Lounge 8-18-2023</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Friday night August 18th I had the pleasure of shooting a buddy’s band, The Side Hustle at The Sky Music Lounge. Here are some of those shots:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/frame/slideshow?key=NZsHcF&amp;amp;speed=3&amp;amp;transition=fade&amp;amp;autoStart=1&amp;amp;captions=0&amp;amp;navigation=0&amp;amp;playButton=0&amp;amp;randomize=0&amp;amp;transitionSpeed=2&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/08/TheSideHustle/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/08/TheSideHustle/</guid>
        
        <category>music</category>
        
        <category>band</category>
        
        <category>rock</category>
        
        <category>Missouri</category>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Add a 2023 MR340 Event WaterMark to your Photos!</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;photomarkco-has-gone-into-hybernation-as-of-9302023-it-may-be-revived-again-in-the-future&quot;&gt;PhotoMark.co has gone into hybernation as of 9/30/2023. It may be revived again in the future.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few weeks before the 2023 MR340 I posted in the Facebook group asking if people wanted the MR340 logo overlaid on the photos from the event. The response was mixed, probably around 50/50, with some people wanting it, and others preferring not to have it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I err’d on the side of not including the logo on the photos that were made available for purchase from the event, but had every intention of figuring out a way to allow the people who wanted the logo, to add the logo, post purchase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I am proud to announce I’ve come up with a way for you to do that!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introducing &lt;a href=&quot;https://PHOTOMARK.CO&quot;&gt;PHOTOMARK.CO&lt;/a&gt;, a simple way for you to add the MR340 logo to your photos from the event. The basics are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://PHOTOMARK.CO&quot;&gt;Visit the website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Upload your photo.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Choose your Logo option (black and gray).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Download the newly generated photo!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s that simple! Though you will need to do this one at a time for each photo you want to add the logo to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t purchased any MR340 photos yet, you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Watersports/MR340&quot;&gt;do so here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently the website is pretty simple, allowing you to choose only from the 2023 MR340 logo options, in the future I might make it a little more customizable to support future, and past, events!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is 100% brand new, custom code, so if you run into any problems, &lt;a href=&quot;https://chrishammond.com/contact&quot;&gt;please don’t hesitate to reach out&lt;/a&gt; with feedback!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/08/PHOTOMARK/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/08/PHOTOMARK/</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>race</category>
        
        <category>paddle</category>
        
        <category>boat</category>
        
        <category>MR340</category>
        
        <category>river</category>
        
        <category>Missouri</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2023 Missouri River Relief MR340 Event Photos</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Watersports/MR340&quot;&gt;The 2023 Missouri River Relief MR340 Event Photos are now available&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a week, what should have been 5 solid days of shooting turned into 2.5 as the weather ended the Missouri River 340 river race on Wednesday afternoon. I made it home that evening and began processing the 10k+ photos I took for the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my first time with the MR340, and I had a blast! Like other events I have participated in, and shot, the MR340 is a family. Everyone is there to help each other out, and have a good time. I was cautious about shooting this event, as I was not sure how the racers would react to me coming in and trying to fill the gap of their previous photographer who was unable to shoot this year. I was pleasantly surprised to find that everyone was very friendly, and happy to see me out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did my best to get a photo of every boat that I could, and tried to get multiple. I most likely missed a few, for that I apologize!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The photos are organized into folders and galleries based on Locations (Check In Day, Start, Napoleon, Waverly, Glasgow, Boonville, Hermann, New Haven, Finish Line Party) and then depending on how many photos I took at a location, also organized into galleries based on windows of time. If you don’t know exactly when you passed through a check point/paddle stop, look at RaceOwl for your splits, then you can check the gallery for that location/time and find the photos of your boat, it is possible you’ll find photos in two time slots depending on how your splits worked out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Watersports/MR340&quot;&gt;View the 2023 MR340 Photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven’t yet committed to being there again next year, it really depends on if I can justify taking a week off of my day job and “working” the event with my photography business! This year was a test, see if I could do it in a way that made financial sense to do so, I haven’t figured out if that’s the case or not yet, but hopefully you all enjoy the photos I took, and specifically enjoy them enough to order some digital downloads or prints!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please don’t hesitate to reach out to me with any feedback you might have, I always love hearing from you all!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for being so welcoming this week and making me feel at home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Chris Hammond, Wildwood, MO&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/08/MR340/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/08/MR340/</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>race</category>
        
        <category>paddle</category>
        
        <category>boat</category>
        
        <category>MR340</category>
        
        <category>river</category>
        
        <category>Missouri</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2023 Miner Tough Weekend</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Year three of shooting the Miner Tough weekend down in St. Joe State Park here in Missouri kicked off with Run The Leadbelt on Saturday July 15th, 2023, followed by the Leadbelt XC Mountain Bike Race on Sunday July 16th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year the event chose to have our photo services available for everyone to have access to free photo downloads! You can &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Miner-Tough-Weekend&quot;&gt;find the photos from the Miner Tough Weekend events now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like you can order prints from our URL above, or you can download the photos and print elsewhere, up to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big thanks to the event organizers for having us out again this year!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/07/MinerTough/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/07/MinerTough/</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>race</category>
        
        <category>trail</category>
        
        <category>run</category>
        
        <category>mtb</category>
        
        <category>mountain bike</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2023 The Freedom 100 Paddle Race</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Our first full paddle race, The Freedom 100 from Boonville Missouri to Jefferson City, Missouri held on Saturday July 8th, 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have shots from the start, at Katfish Katy’s and then the finish line. Apologies if we missed you, tried to get multiple shots of every competitor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click the link below to access all the galleries with purchase options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2023/Watersports/The-Freedom-Race-100&quot;&gt;Photos Available to View and Purchase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/07/Freedom100/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://rainbowmarks.com/Events/2023/07/Freedom100/</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        <category>padding</category>
        
        <category>boat</category>
        
        <category>race</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
